Guide to the U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
U.S. Department of Labor Office of American Workplace Labor Management Cooperation Collected Publications
- Sweden Works - Trist, Eric., Publication (Box 24)
  - Teitelbaum, Richard S. "Are Times Tough? Here's the Answer", Publication (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Are Times Tough? Here's an Answer, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 44)
      Author: Richard S. Teitelbaum
  - Tella, Alfred, "The Relation of Labor Force to Employment", Publication (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: The Relation of Labor Force to Employment, 1964; Publication (Box 24, Folder 45)
      Author: Alfred Tella
  - "Tenneco Implements Quality Circles", Publication (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Item 1: Teneco Implements Quality Circles, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 46)
  - Teresko, John, "Challenging Traditions", Publication (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Item 1: Challenging Traditions, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 47)
      Author: John Teresko
  - Terleckyj, Nestor E., "Demography and Changes in the U.S. Labor Force", Publication (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Item 1: Demography and Changes in the U.S. Labor Force, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 48)
      Author: Nestor E. Terleckyj
  - Tewell, Rich, "How to Keep Quality Circles in Motion", Publication (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Item 1: How to Keep Quality Circles in Motion, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 49)
      Author: Rich Tewell
  - The Texas Center for Productivity and Quality of Work Life, Publication (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Item 1: Data-Based Team Development: Concepts, Structures, Strategies and Measurement-Working Paper #10, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - "The Coming Industrial Miracle", Publication (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Item 1: The Coming Industrial Miracle, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - The Conference Board. Human Resources Outlook 1989, Publication (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Item 1: Human Resources Outlook 1989, 1988; Publication (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - "The Economy of the 1990s: What the Sober Spenders Will Buy", Publication (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Item 1: The Economy of the 1990s: What the Sober Spenders Will Buy, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Personnel Administrator, "The Flip Side", Publication (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Item 1: The Flip Side, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - The Human Connection: Making Organizations Work, Publication (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Item 1: The Human Connection: Making Organizations Work, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - "The Income Security Dilemma: Aid or Obstacle to Productivity", Publication (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Item 1: The Income Security Dilemma: Aid or Obstacle to Productivity, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - "The Individual Within the Organization", Publication (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Item 1: The Individual Within the Organization, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 57)
  - "The JANCO ESOP", Publication (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Item 1: The JANCO ESOP, Publication (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - "The New Industrial Relations", Publication (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Item 1: The New Industrial Relations, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - "The Politics of Privatization", Publication (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Item 1: The Politics of Privatization, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 60)
  - The Productivity Forum, 1982 Insiders Meeting, Publication (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Item 1: 1982 Insiders Meeting, Publication (Box 24, Folder 61)
  - The Productivity Forum, Productivity Through Work Innovations: Executive Summary, Publication (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Item 1: Productivity Through Work Innovations: Executive Summary, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - The Productivity Forum, Report of the First Insider Working Session--Florida, Publication (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Item 1: Report of the First Insider Working Session- Florida, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - "The Revival of Productivity", Publication (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Item 1: The Revival of Productivity, 1984; Publication (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - "The Speedup in Automation", Publication (Box 24, Folder 65)
    - Item 1: The Speedup in Automation, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 65)
  - "The Tax Magic That's Making Employee Stock Plans Multiply", Publication (Box 24, Folder 66)
    - Item 1: The Tax Magic That's Making Employee, 1984; Publication (Box 24, Folder 66)
  - Thimm, Alfred L., "How Far Should German Codetermination Go?", Publication (Box 24, Folder 67)
    - Item 1: How Far Should German Codetermination Go?, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 67)
      Author: Alfred L. Thimm
  - Thomas, Clarence, "Minorities, Youth, and Education", Publication (Box 24, Folder 68)
    - Item 1: Minorities, Youth, and Education, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 68)
      Author: Clarence Thomas
  - Thomas, Edward G., "Flexible Work Keeps Growing", Publication (Box 24, Folder 69)
    - Item 1: Flexible Work Keeps Growing, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 69)
      Author: Edward G. Thomas
  - Thomas, R. Roosevelt, Jr., "From Affirmative Action to Affirming Diversity", Publication (Box 24, Folder 70)
    - Item 1: From Affirmative Action to Affirming Diversity, 1990; Publication (Box 24, Folder 70)
      Author: R. Roosevelt Thomas, Jr.
  - Thompson, Brad Lee. "Negotiating Training- Win-Win or What?", Publication (Box 24, Folder 71)
    - Item 1: Negotiating Training- Win-Win or What?, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 71)
      Author: Brad Lee Thompson
  - Thompson, Donald B., "Back to Basics", Publication (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - Item 1: Back to Basics, 1984; Publication (Box 24, Folder 72)
      Author: Donald B. Thompson
  - Thompson, Donald, "New Role for Labor Unions?", Publication (Box 24, Folder 73)
    - Item 1: New Role for Labor Unions?, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 73)
      Author: Donald Thompson
  - Thompson, Donald B., "Steel Launches an 'Invisible' Revolution", Publication (Box 24, Folder 74)
    - Item 1: Steel Launches an 'Invisible' Revolution, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 74)
  - Thompson, John A., The Second Wave of Educational Reform: Implications for School Leadership, Administration and Organization, Publication (Box 24, Folder 75)
    - Item 1: The Second Wave of Educational Reform: Implications for School Leadership, Administration and Organization, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 75)
      Author: John A. Thompson
  - Thompson, Linda, "New Office Technology and the Changing Role of the Secretary", Publication (Box 24, Folder 76)
    - Item 1: New Office Technology and the Changing Role of the Secretary, 1989; Publication (Box 24, Folder 76)
      Author: Linda Thompson
  - Thompson, Paul H., Baker, Robin Zenger, et al. "Improving Professional Development by Applying the Four Stage Career Model", Publication (Box 24, Folder 77)
    - Item 1: Improving Professional Development by Applying the Four-Stage Career Model, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 77)
      Author: Paul H. Thompson, Robin Zenger Baker, Norman Smallwood
  - Thompson, Robert T., Jr., "Labor Productivity and Employee Relations", Publication (Box 24, Folder 78)
    - Item 1: Labor Productivity and Employee Relations, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 78)
      Author: Robert T. Thompson, Jr.
  - Thompson, Roger, "Caring for the Children", Publication (Box 24, Folder 79)
    - Item 1: Caring for the Children, 1988; Publication (Box 24, Folder 79)
      Author: Roger Thompson
  - Thompson, Roger. "States Adopt Fee Schedules", Publication (Box 24, Folder 80)
    - Item 1: States Adopt Fee Schedules, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Thor, Carl, "Conducting an Industry-Level Benchmarking Study", Publication (Box 24, Folder 81)
    - Item 1: Conducting an Industry-Level Benchmarking Study, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 81)
      Author: Carl Thor
  - Thor, Carl G., "Knowledge Worker Gain Sharing", Publication (Box 24, Folder 82)
    - Item 1: Knowledge Worker Gain Sharing, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 82)
      Author: Carl G. Thor
  - Thor, Carl G., Perspectives 1989, Publication (Box 24, Folder 83)
    - Item 1: Perspectives 1989, Publication (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Perspectives 90, Publication (Box 24, Folder 84)
    - Item 1: Perspectives 90, 1990; Publication (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Thor, Carl, Perspectives '91, Publication (Box 24, Folder 85)
    - Item 1: Perspectives '91, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Thor, Carl G., Perspectives '92, Publication (Box 24, Folder 86)
    - Item 1: Perspectives '92, 1992; Publication (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Thor, Carl G., Productivity Perspectives, Publication (Box 24, Folder 87)
    - Item 1: Productivity Perspectives, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Thor, Carl G., Productivity Perspectives: 1987 Edition, Publication (Box 24, Folder 88)
    - Item 1: Productivity Perspectives: 1987 Edition, Publication (Box 24, Folder 88)
  - Thor, Carl, "Measuring the Maintenance Department", Publication (Box 24, Folder 89)
    - Item 1: Measuring the Maintenance Department, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 89)
  - Thor, Carl G., "Productivity: A Key Element of Corporate Reporting", Publication (Box 24, Folder 90)
    - Item 1: Productivity: A Key Element of Corporate Reporting, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 90)
  - Thor, Carl G., "Productivity Perspectives", Publication (Box 24, Folder 91)
    - Item 1: Productivity Perspectives, 1988; Publication (Box 24, Folder 91)
  - Thorsteinson, Tim and Mary Storms, "A 'Quest' for Productivity", Publication (Box 24, Folder 92)
    - Item 1: A 'Quest' for Productivity, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 92)
      Author: Tim Thorsteinson and Mary Storms
  - Thorbeck, John "The Turnaround Value of Values", Publication (Box 24, Folder 93)
    - Item 1: The Turnaround Value of Values, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 93)
      Author: John Thorbeck
  - Thurow, Lester, "Producer Economics", Publication (Box 24, Folder 94)
    - Item 1: Producer Economics, 1988; Publication (Box 24, Folder 94)
      Author: Lester Thurow
  - Thurow, Lester C., "Restoring U.S. Productivity: A Public Framework for Private Action", Publication (Box 24, Folder 95)
    - Item 1: Restoring U.S. Productivity: A Public Framework for Private Action, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 95)
      Author: Lester C. Thurow
  - Thurow, Lester and Louise Waldstein, Toward a High-Wage, High-Productivity Service Sector, Publication (Box 24, Folder 96)
    - Item 1: Toward a High-Wage, High-Productivity Service Sector, 1989; Publication (Box 24, Folder 96)
      Author: Lester Thurow and Louise Waldstein
  - Tichy, Noel and David Ulrich, "Revitalizing Organizations: The Leadership Role", Publication (Box 24, Folder 97)
    - Item 1: Revitalizing Organizations: The Leadership Role, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 97)
      Author: Noel Tichy and David Ulrich
  - Tichy, Noel M., "When Does Work Restructuring Work?", Publication (Box 24, Folder 98)
    - Item 1: When Does Work Restructuring Work? Organizational Innovations at Volvo and GM, 1976; Publication (Box 24, Folder 98)
      Author: Noel M. Tichy
  - Tierno, David A., "SM Forum: Growth Strategies for Consulting in the Next Decade", Publication (Box 24, Folder 99)
    - Item 1: SMR Forum: Growth Strategies for Consulting in the Next Decade, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 99)
      Author: David A. Tierno and Arthur Young
  - Tilly, Chris, Short Hours, Publication (Box 24, Folder 100)
    - Item 1: Short Hours, Short Shrift: Causes and Consequences of Part-Time Work, 1990; Publication (Box 24, Folder 100)
      Author: Chris Tilly
  - Timm, Paul R., "Let's Not Have a Meeting", Publication (Box 24, Folder 101)
    - Item 1: Let's not have a meeting!, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 101)
      Author: Paul R. Timm
  - Todd, John O., "Employee Stock Ownership Trusts", Publication (Box 24, Folder 102)
    - Item 1: Employee Stock Ownership Trusts, Publication (Box 24, Folder 102)
      Author: John O. Todd
  - Tomasko, Robert M., "Managing Compensation Strategically: Focusing Company Reward Systems to Help Achieve Business Objectives", Publication (Box 24, Folder 103)
    - Item 1: Managing Compensation Strategically: Focusing Company Reward Systems to Help Achieve Business Objectives, 1982; Publication (Box 24, Folder 103)
      Author: Robert M. Tomasko
  - Tomasko, Robert M., "Restructuring: Getting it Right", Publication (Box 24, Folder 104)
    - Item 1: Restructuring: Getting it Right, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 104)
  - Tomaskovic-Devey, Donald and S.M. Miller, "Can High-Tech Provide the Jobs?", Publication (Box 24, Folder 105)
    - Item 1: Can High-Tech Provide the Jobs?, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 105)
      Author: Donald Tomaskovic-Devey and S.M. Miller
  - Torrence, William D., "Plant Closing and Advance Notice: Another Look at Numbers", Publication (Box 24, Folder 106)
    - Item 1: Plant Closing and Advance Notice: Another Look at the Numbers, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 106)
      Author: William D. Torrence
  - Tortorich, R., P. Thompson, D. Layfield, C. Dreyfus and M. Kelley, "Measuring Organizational Impact of Quality Circles", Publication (Box 24, Folder 107)
    - Item 1: Measuring Organizational Impact of Quality Circles, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 107)
      Author: R. Tortorich, P. Thompson, D. Layfield, C. Orfan, C. Dreyfus, and M. Kelley
  - Toscano, David J., "Employee Ownership and Democracy in the Workplace", Publication (Box 24, Folder 108)
    - Item 1: Employee Ownership and Democracy in the Workplace, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 108)
      Author: David J. Toscano
  - Toscano, David J., "Labor-Management Cooperation and West German System of Codetermination", Publication (Box 24, Folder 109)
    - Item 1: Labor-Management Cooperation and the West German System of Codetermination, 1981; Publication (Box 24, Folder 109)
  - Toshiba Consumer Products, About CoAB, Publication (Box 24, Folder 110)
    - Item 1: About CoAB, Publication (Box 24, Folder 110)
  - "Toshiba's Big Switch", Publication (Box 24, Folder 111)
    - Item 1: Toshiba's Big Switch, Publication (Box 24, Folder 111)
  - Tosi, Henry and Lisa Tosi, "What Managers Need to Know About Knowledge-Based Pay", Publication (Box 24, Folder 112)
    - Item 1: What Managers Need to Know About Knowledge-Based Pay, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 112)
      Author: Henry Tosi and Lisa Tosi
  - Tourangeau, Kevin W., "Downsizing: A Structured Approach for Lasting Gains", Publication (Box 24, Folder 113)
    - Item 1: Downsizing: A Structured Approach for Lasting Gains, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 113)
      Author: Kevin W. Tourangeau
  - "Towards Excellence in the Public Sector: How can we achieve it", Publication (Box 24, Folder 114)
    - Item 1: Towards Excellence in the Public Sector: How Can We Achieve it, 1985; Publication (Box 24, Folder 114)
  - Towers, Perrin. After the Paychecks End: Financing the Retirement Years, Publication (Box 24, Folder 115)
    - Item 1: After the Paychecks End: Financing the Retirement Years, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 115)
  - Towers, Perrin, "A Day in the Life: Working in the 90s", Publication (Box 24, Folder 116)
    - Item 1: A Day in the Life: Working in the '90's, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 116)
  - Towers, Perrin, Paying for Skill and Knowledge: Experiences from the Front Lines-- A Report on Skill-Based Pay, Publication (Box 24, Folder 117)
    - Item 1: Paying for Skill and Knowledge: Experiences from the Front-Lines- A Report on Skill-Based Pay, 1992; Publication (Box 24, Folder 117)
  - Towers, Perrin, United States Participants' Report: Worldwide Human Resources Leadership Study, Publication (Box 24, Folder 118)
    - Item 1: United States' Participants' Report: Worldwide Human Resources Leadership Study, Publication (Box 24, Folder 118)
  - Towers, Perrin, Workforce 2000 Today: A Bottom-Line Concern, Publication (Box 24, Folder 119)
    - Item 1: Workforce 2000 Today: A Bottom-Line Concern, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 119)
  - Towers, Perrin, Word-for-Word, Publication (Box 24, Folder 120)
    - Item 1: Word-for-Word, 1990; Publication (Box 24, Folder 120)
  - Towers, Perrin and the Hudson Institute, Workforce 2000: Competing in a Seller's Market: Is Corporate America Prepared?, Publication (Box 24, Folder 121)
    - Item 1: Workforce 2000: Competing in a Seller's Market: Is Corporate America Prepared?, 1990; Publication (Box 24, Folder 121)
  - Townsend, Patrick L. and Gebhardt, Joan E., "Creating More Creativity", Publication (Box 24, Folder 122)
    - Item 1: Creating More Creativity, 1991; Publication (Box 24, Folder 122)
      Author: Patrick L. Townsend and Joan E. Gebhardt
  - Townsend, Patrick "White Collar Quality-The Paul Revere Approach", Publication (Box 24, Folder 123)
    - Item 1: Quality- Down to the Roots, 1990; Publication (Box 24, Folder 123)
  - Toyoda, Eiji, "Mutual Benefits: International Industrial Competition and Cooperative", Publication (Box 24, Folder 124)
    - Item 1: White Collar Quality- The Paul Revere Approach, 1985; Publication (Box 24, Folder 124)
      Author: Patrick Townsend
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen Joel, "Community Colleges: Education, Training and retraining the American Work Force for the New Decade", Publication (Box 24, Folder 125)
    - Item 1: Mutual Benefits: International Industrial Competition and Cooperative, 1988; Publication (Box 24, Folder 125)
      Author: Eiji Toyoda
  - "Transcripts for Midland-Ross", Publication (Box 24, Folder 126)
    - Item 1: Community Colleges: Education, Training, and Retraining the American Work Force for the New Decade, 1992; Publication (Box 24, Folder 126)
      Author: Stephen Joel Trachtenberg
  - Treece, James B., "Here Comes GM's Saturn", Publication (Box 24, Folder 127)
    - Item 1: Transcripts for Midland-Ross, 1976; Publication (Box 24, Folder 127)
  - Treece, James B. Miller, Karen Lowry Melcher, Richard A., "The Partners", Publication (Box 24, Folder 128)
    - Item 1: Here Comes GM's Saturn, 1990; Publication (Box 24, Folder 128)
      Author: James B. Treece
  - Tregoe, Benjamin B., "Productivity in America: Where it Went and How to Get it Back", Publication (Box 24, Folder 129)
    - Item 1: The Partners, 1992; Publication (Box 24, Folder 129)
      Author: James B. Treece, Karen Lowry Miller, Richard A. Melcher
  - Government Employee Relations Report, "Trends in Teacher Bargaining", Publication (Box 24, Folder 130)
    - Item 1: Productivity in America: Where It Went and How to Get It Back, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 130)
      Author: Benjamin B. Tregoe
  - Trepainer, Peter J. and Gary K. Francis, "Uniting to Revive a Declining Industry: Perspectives on the Armco Ashland Works Experience", Publication (Box 24, Folder 131)
    - Item 1: Trends in Teacher Bargaining, Publication (Box 24, Folder 131)
  - Treu, Tiziano, "Collective Bargaining in Italy: Recent Trends and Problems", Publication (Box 24, Folder 132)
    - Item 1: Uniting to Revive a Declining Industry: Perspectives on the Armco Ashland Works Experience, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 132)
      Author: Peter J. Trepanier and Gary K. Francis
  - Treu, Tiziano, "Equal Pay and Comparable Worth: A View From Europe", Publication (Box 24, Folder 133)
    - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in Italy: Recent Trends and Problems, 1987; Publication (Box 24, Folder 133)
      Author: Tiziano Treu
  - Treu, Tiziano, "New Trends in Worktime Issues: Introduction", Publication (Box 24, Folder 134)
    - Item 1: Equal Pay and Comparable Worth: A View from Europe, 1986; Publication (Box 24, Folder 134)
  - Treu, Tiziano, "The Role of Neutrals in the Resolution of Interest Disputes in Italy", Publication (Box 24, Folder 135)
    - Item 1: New Trends in Worktime Issues: Introduction, 1989; Publication (Box 24, Folder 135)
  - Tribus, Myron, "Creating the Competitive Organization", Publication (Box 24, Folder 136)
    - Item 1: The Role of Neutrals in the Resolution of Interest Disputes in Italy, 1989; Publication (Box 24, Folder 136)
  - Tribus, Myron, "Deming's Way", Publication (Box 24, Folder 137)
    - Item 1: Creating the Competitive Organization, 1992; Publication (Box 24, Folder 137)
      Author: Myron Tribus
  - Trice, Harrison and Janice M. Beyer, "A Study of Union-Management cooperation in a Long Standing Alcoholism Program", Publication (Box 24, Folder 138)
    - Item 1: Deming's Way, 1984; Publication (Box 24, Folder 138)
  - "A Winning Trio", Publication (Box 24, Folder 139)
    - Item 1: A Study of Union-Management Cooperation in a Long-Standing Alcoholism Program, 1983; Publication (Box 24, Folder 139)
      Author: Harrison Trice and Janice M. Beyer
  - Trist, Eric, "Collaboration in Work Setting: A Personal Perspective", Publication (Box 24, Folder 140)
    - Item 1: A Winning Trio, 1985; Publication (Box 24, Folder 140)
- Trist, Eric "Improving" - United States General Accounting Office., Publication (Box 25)
  - Trist, Eric, Improving Productivity and Quality of Working Life in the Public Sector: Pioneering Initiatives in Labor-Management Cooperation, Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Improving Productivity and Quality of Working Life in the Public Sector: Pioneering Initiatives in Labor-Management Cooperation, 1980; Publication (Box 25, Folder 1)
      Author: Eric Trist
  - Trist, Eric, The Evolution of Socio-Technical Systems: A Conceptual Framework and an Action Research Program, Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: The Evolution of Socio-technical Systems: A Conceptual Framework and an Action Research Program, 1981; Publication (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Trist, Eric, "QWL and the '80s", Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: QWL and the 80's, 1981; Publication (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Trist, Eric and William A. Westley, QWL in the Federal Public Sector, Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: QWL in the Federal Public Sector, 1982; Publication (Box 25, Folder 4)
      Author: Eric Trist and William A. Wesley
  - Trowbridge, Alexander B., "Human Resource Issues in the 1980's", Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: Human Resources in the 1980s, 1982; Publication (Box 25, Folder 5)
      Author: Alexander B. Trowbridge
  - Troy, Katherine L., Employee Communications: New Top-Management Priority, Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Employee Communications: New Top-Management Priority, 1988; Publication (Box 25, Folder 6)
      Author: Katherine L. Troy
  - Troy, Leo, "Convergence in International Unionism, etc.: The Case of Canada and the USA", Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Convergence in International Unionism, etc.: The Case of Canada and the USA, 1992; Publication (Box 25, Folder 7)
      Author: Leo Troy
  - Troy, Leo. "Is the U.S. Unique in the Decline of Private Sector Unionism?", Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Is the U.S. Unique in the Decline of Private Sector Unionism?, 1990; Publication (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Troy, Leo, Distribution of Union Membership Among the States 1939 and 1953, Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Distribution of Union Membership among the States 1939 and 1953, 1957; Publication (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Troy, Leo and Neil Sheflin, "The Flow and Ebb of U.S. Public Sector Unionism", Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: The Flow and Ebb of U.S. Public Sector Unionism, 1984; Publication (Box 25, Folder 10)
      Author: Leo Troy and Neil Sheflin
  - "TRW Leads a Revolution in Managing Technology", Publication (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: TRW Leads a Revolution in Managing Technology, 1982; Publication (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Tsuda, Masumi, "Human Resource Development and New Technology in the Automobile Industry--The Japanese Case", Publication (Box 25, Folder 12)